

\times

shah.bhakti159@gmail.com



+91-8080373850



B/307, Venkatesh Darshan, Venkatesh Park, Phatak Road, Bhayandar (West), Mumbai, India



animplicitsoul.wordpress.co m

in

linkedin.com/in/bhakti-shah-3b884615a



instagram.com/animplicitsoul

SKILLS

Content Writing,
Blogging, Social
Media Marketing,
Search Engine
Marketing, Website
Development, Email
Marketing, Basics of
C++, MySQL &
HTML, Well versed
with Microsoft Office
(Word, Excel, and
Power point)

LANGUAGES

English, Hindi, Gujarati, Marathi











INTERESTS

Music, Dancing, Reading Novels, Badminton, Photography.

Bhakti Shah

Digital Marketer & Content Writer

An ambitious digital marketer looking forward to explore more into digital era. Worked with various companies in different fields and gained decent experience. Now looking forward to grab opportunity in Content as well as digital marketing and look after personal as well the organizations growth.

WORK EXPERIENCE

PROJECTS DONE RECENTLY (AS A FREELANCER)

Articles on Crypto Currency for Bank of Hodlers (Bangalore)

Articles for Healspace Healthcare (California)

Facebook Ads for Appen Global (Australia)

Realtors project for a client (Canada)

Data Development (USA)

Social Media Campaign for Foto trails (Bangalore)

Blogging on Insurance for En Casa Artomotive (Gurgaon)

CURRENT ONGOING PROJECT

Blogs for Grove86 LLC (United States)
Website Content & Blogs for Team Invent (Mumbai)

Title/Position

Wipro InfoTech - Assistant Media Manager

05/2016 - 10/2016

Title/Position

ICICI Prudential Life Insurance - Financial Service Consultant

12/2015 - 03/2016

Title/Position

RSM Astute Consulting - Internal Auditor

08/2015 - 10/2015

EDUCATION

6 month Professional Course in Digital Marketing IIDE

M.com

Currently Pursuing from Mumbai University (Part1 cleared)

B.com (2013 – 2015)

MPVV College of Commerce

H.S.C (2010 – 2012)

SVDV Junior College of Commerce

S.S.C (2009-2010)

The Don Bosco High School